那是什么
What's that?
Faraday给我画的草图
Cheat sheet faraday drew for me.
你不知道你们的船在哪?
You don't know where your boat is?
我知道
I know where it is.
那为什么你径直的朝雷暴云的地方飞
Why are you flying directly into the thunderhead?
你就不能安稳的坐着  让我自己搞定吗
Why don't you just sit back and let me do my job, huh?
她就是Penelope?
Is that penelope?
她给Charlie说她不知道这艘船  是吗
She told charlie she didn't know about this boat, correct?
对
Aye.
-你想在那找到什么  -答案
What do you expect to find when you get there? answers.
糟糕
Damn it!
坐稳了
Hold on!
全体立正
On your soddin' feet!
快  快  快
Move! move! move!
你还在干嘛  Hume
What are you waiting for, hume?
你怎么了  Hume
What's the matter, hume?
没听见我说话吗?
Did you not hear me?
抱歉长官  我...  我刚才做梦了
I'm sorry, sir. I was-- I was having a dream, sir.
你做梦了?!
You were having a dream, were you?
你梦见什么了
And what were you dreaming about?
让你慢吞吞的准备好
That it took you so sodding long to get to your mark?!
我梦见自己在一架直升飞机上  长官
I was in a helicopter, sir,
风暴来袭  长官
And there was a storm, sir.
还有...
And...
我不记得其他的了  长官
I don't remember the rest, sir.
至少还是个他妈的关于军队的梦
Well, at least it was a bloody military dream.
好!  你们所有人
Right! all of ya!
立刻到操场  4分钟之内集合
In the yard! four minutes!
你们可以私下里感谢Hume
And you can thank private hume
他让你们的操练时间增加两倍
For having to do it in double-time.
快!  一!  二!  三!
Move! one, two, three!
三!  一!  二!  三!
Three! one, two, three!
四!  一!  二!  三!
Four! one, two, three!
五!
Five.
100个仰卧起坐  快  快  快
100 crunches! go! go! go! go! go!
一!  二!  三!
One! two! three...
我希望为了你的梦值得做这些  伙计
I hope your dream was worth this, mate.
抱歉兄弟  只是...
Sorry, pal. it's just...
从没有过如此真实的梦
I've never had a dream that was so vivid.
就好象...好象我真的在那
It was--it was like I was actually there.
你要发表什么意见吗  Hume?
have you got something to say, Hume?
我在问你话!
I asked you a question!
就要通过了
We're almost through it.
我看到阳光了
I see daylight.
你知道你在做什么吗?
What do you think you're doing?
Desmond  你还好吧?
Desmond, are you all right?
你是谁
Who are you?
你怎么知道我的名字
How do you know my name?!
声明：本字幕由YYeTs人人影视字幕组原创翻译制作
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎登录人人影视论坛交流 下载 在线观看 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：爱爱  paradise  小帝  许愿
时间轴：leolou456  不爱
字幕总监制：何何  后期： 梁良
来
Here you go.
好吧  他们一天前走的
All right, they took off a day ago.
为什么到现在还没有消息
Why haven't we heard from 'em?
我再给你说一遍
I'm gonna tell you again,
医生  一晚上我都给你说了我也不知道啊
As I've been telling you all night, doctor, I don't know!
我给船上通话的内容你也听到了
You heard the same thing as I did when we called the boat.
-你凭什么认为我知道些什么  -因为你不担心
What makes you think I know anything? because you're not worried.
什么?
Excuse me?
你们的船离这里40英里
Your boat's 40 miles off the coast.
只用花20分钟就到了
It should've taken 'em, what, 20 minutes to get there?
-你为什么一点也不担心  -那我是不是应该
So why aren't you worried? well, should I wring my hands together
双手祈祷他们不要出事呢
And whisper a prayer on their behalf?
别这样
Hey, hey, hey. come on.
要不我们...直接告诉他们
Maybe we should just-- just tell 'em.
告诉我们什么
Tell us what?
Dan...别让他们更晕了
Dan... let's not confuse anyone.
Daniel  也许你讲慢一点
Well... daniel, maybe if you talk real slow,
我们能听懂
We'll be able to follow.
你们所感知的你们朋友离开了多久
Your perception of how long your friends have been gone...
其实并不是他们实际就离开了那么久
It's not necessarily how long they've actually been gone.
什么意思
What does that mean?
就不该这样
This is a mistake.
没事的
It'll be fine. it'll be fine.
Frank只要按照我给他的方位图飞行
As long as frank flew on the bearings that I gave him,
他按照那个来飞行的话...就会没事
If he stayed on it, it... it'll be fine.
如果他没有呢
And what if he didn't?
那可能就会出现些副作用
Then there might be side effects.
-我们在2000英尺的高空  坐好了  -我在这干嘛
We're at 2,000 feet. sit down! what am I doing here?!
-到底是怎么了  -Desmond有点不对劲
What the hell's going on?! something's wrong with desmond.
-你怎么知道我的名字?  -让他坐稳了
How do you know my name?! hold him in his seat!
-我不是在做吗  -让我离开
I'm trying! let go of me!
别让他碰着操纵杆了  我们还有两分钟到达
Keep him away from the stick! we'll be there in two minutes!
你回来干嘛?  他们是谁
What are you doing back? who are they?
大洋航班815的幸存者
Survivors of 815.
你把他们带到这里  你到底在想什么?
So you brought them here. what the hell were you thinking?
我在哪?
Where--where am i?
-好了  放松  -你们是谁
All right, just take it easy. who are you people?
放松  伙计
buddy. okay, now, take it easy, buddy.
-我为什么会在这  你们是谁  -我朋友有点失常了
what am I doing here? who are you people? my friend is disoriented.
我不是你的朋友  我根本不认识你
Look, I'm not your friend! I don't know you!
他什么时候开始这样的
when did he start doing this?
我们起飞的时候还好好的  当遇见暴风时...
He was fine when we took off. when we hit some weather--
Faraday告诉我只要按照他的方向
Hey, faraday told me as long as I stayed on the vector
等等
wait.
你叫什么  朋友
What's your name, my friend?
-Sayid  -好的Sayid  我们要把你的兄弟
Sayid. okay, sayid. look, we're gonna take your buddy
带到下面的医务室  好吗
Down to the sick bay, okay?
-我和他一起  -让我们的医生先照顾他吧
I'm going with him. let our doctor look at him first,
然后你再下来也行
Then you can come down.
我答应你  好吗
You got my word on that, okay?
听着  这一定是哪里弄错了
hey, listen to me-- th-this is a mistake, right?
我不认识这些人
I don't know these people.
我真的不认识这些人
不  这一定是弄错了
No, but this is wrong!
我不应该在这
I'm not supposed to be here.
20!  21!
20! 21.
22!  这?
22. "here"?
"这"什么
"here" what?
你在那站着干嘛
What the hell are you doing on your feet?
做完仰卧起坐了?
Are you finished with your crunches
你想跑步了?
Because you want to run?!
好!  集合
Right! squad!
立正
On your feet!
向右转!
Right face!
10公里!
10 kilometers!
快!  快!  快!
Go! go! go! go! go! go! go!
-跑起来  -帮帮我  我受不了了
Get moving, or so help me, I'll kill you myself.
你是怎么了  Des
What the hell's the matter with you, des?
我告诉你的话  你一定认为我疯了
If I told you, you'd think I was crazy.
我已经认为你疯了
I already know you're crazy.
今天早晨
This morning,
当我在操场做仰卧起坐的时候
When I was in the yard doing crunches...
我离开了
I left.
什么意思  你离开了?
What do you mean, you left?
我在一艘船上
I was on a boat.
然后又回来了  就在开始的地方
And then--then I was back here, right--right where I started.
Des  如果你想逃脱军役的话
Des, if you're trying to get tossed out of service--
Billy伙计  我说的都是真的
Billy, I am telling you the truth, man.
船上还有什么人
Who else was on this... boat?
有你认识的吗
Anyone you recognize?
Penny
Penny.
有张照片  Penny在里面
There was a photo. penny was in the photo.
什么?
What?
Des  你去哪
des! where you going?!
今天早上真多亏了你  Hume
Thanks for this morning, hume.
小心点
watch your step.
小心点  放松
Watch it. watch your step. take it easy.
我不在这儿
I'm not here.
这...
This...
这...不可能
This--this isn't happening.
你在这  这是可能的
You are here, and this is happening.
-我们要照顾你  -我在这干嘛
Look, we're gonna take care of you. w-what am I doing here?
-没关系  你会好起来的  -我不应该在这
It's all right. you're gonna be okay. I'm not supposed to be here.
你们是谁
Who are you people?
我是Keamy  这是Omar
My name is keamy, and this is omar.
我来自拉斯维加斯  他是佛罗里达的
I'm from vegas, and he's from florida.
但要问我们在哪  我们上次停靠在斐济
But as for where we are, i-- we last ported in fiji.
至少我们还在太平洋上
So at least we know we're still in the pacific.
好的  伙计放松
All right, my friend. now you just relax, okay?
我们去把医生找来
We're gonna go get the doc,
他要问你一些问题
And he's gonna wanna ask you some questions
-帮助我们一起理清楚  -理清楚是什么意思
To--to help us sort all this out. wh-what do you mean, "sort out"?
等等  你是什么意思  我不应该在这里
Wait a minute. what do you mean? I'm not supposed to be here!
我不应该在这里  开门  开门
I'm not supposed to be here! open this door! open this door!
也在你身上发生了  是吗
It's happening to you, too, isn't it?
Desmond怎么了
What's happening to Desmond?
你的朋友知道他怎么了
Your friends know what's wrong with him.
就算他们知道  他们也不会给我说的
Well, if they do, they're not sharing it with me.
但你会给他们说我们怎样蒙蒙亮就从岛上起飞
Then perhaps you'll share how we took off at dusk
怎样在中午降落  是吗
And landed in the middle of the day?
听着  我不知道
Listen, I don't know
你的伙伴发生了什么事
What's happening to your buddy, all right?
但你得相信我说的话
But you gotta trust me when I tell you this.
我是在努力帮你
I am trying to help you.
你要帮助我?
You want to help me?
把你的电话给我
Give me your phone.
我要和我的人通话
Let me call my people.
你给我那把枪  我就给你电话
You give me that weapon, and I'll give you this phone.
快点  不要试图打到巴格达
Be quick. don't go trying to call baghdad.
那种电话只能互相呼叫
Those phones only call each other.
是Jack吗  我是Sayid
Jack? it's Sayid.
我现在在货船上
I'm on the freighter.
你还好吗  你们到底在哪
Are you okay? where the hell have you been?
飞行中出了点事
Something happened during the flight,
Desmond现在在船上的医务室里
And now Desmond's in their sick bay.
别挂  别挂  别挂
Hold on. hold on, hold on, hold on.
好了  扬声器开了可以说了
All right, you're on speaker.
在直升机上  Desmond出了点事
On the helicopter, something happened to Desmond.
他看起来好象不认识我  也不知道他在哪
He doesn't appear to recognize me or know where he is.
是坐了飞机后的副作用吗
"side effects"?
等等  你的朋友Desmond  他...
Wait, your friend, um, Desmond--has he...
他最近遭受过高辐射吗
Has he recently been exposed to high levels of radiation
或者是电磁辐射
Or electromagnetism?
我们也不知道为什么
Okay, look, uh, we don't know why,
但是有些人离开或来到这个岛
But going to and coming from the island,
就会感觉...有点困惑
Some people can get a little... confused.
什么  是健忘症吗
What? this is amnesia?
不是  这不是健忘症
No, this is not amnesia.
嘿
Hey.
嘿!
Hey. hey!
能听到我说话吗
Can you hear me?!
你还好吗
Are you all right?!
喂!
Hello?!
我刚刚在大观览车
I was just on a ferris wheel.
瞧  Ray  我没有疯
See, ray? I'm not crazy.
他也这样了  你们很快也会发生这样的事
It's happening to him, too, ray, and it's gonna happen to you.
你们所有人都会发生  每个人...
It's gonna happen to all of us, everyone...
只要我们再去那个岛
Once we start heading to that island again.
你能让开一下吗
Would you please step aside?
不要  不要  Ray
No. no. ray, no.
-我要你放松一会儿  -不
I need you to relax for a minute. no.
不  已经无法阻止  Ray!
No, it's not gonna stop it, ray!
无法阻止  Ray!  什么也无法阻止!
Nothing can stop it, ray! nothing can stop it!
-你感觉怎样  -该死的  这到底是怎么回事
And how are you feeling? what the bloody hell is going on?!
-你现在很迷惑  我能理解  -你胆敢那样对我
I understand you're disoriented. you're not gonna stick me with that,
我不会强制做任何事
I... don't wanna stick you with anything.
没事  我只想检查一下你的眼睛
It's okay. I just wanna check your eyes.
这样我才能帮助你
So I can help you.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
Desmond
Desmond.
Desmond  你为何不给我讲一讲你能记得的最后一件事
Desmond, why don't you tell me about the last thing you remem--
是Penny吗
Penny?
你想干啥  Desmond
What do you want, Desmond?
Penny  听着  我...
Um, Penny, listen, I'm, uh...
我现在有麻烦  而且...
I'm in trouble, and, uh...
但是我...我想我身上发生了一些事  而且...
But i... I think something's happening to me, and...
我现在很迷惑  还有...
I'm confused and...
我...我想见见你
I... I need to see you.
你已经和我断绝关系了  后来你又参军了
You broke off with me, and then you joined the army,
现在你又满怀期望给我打电话
And now you call with some expectation
你以为我还在乎你吗?
That I still care about you?
我确实认为你很迷惑  Desmond
Yeah, I'd say you are confused, Desmond.
不  不  我不是  只是  只是...
No, no, I'm not. it's--it's...
今晚开始  我就有两天假
Look, i-i've got two days leave starting tonight.
我能不能去看看你
Can i--can i-- can I come and see you?
不!  也不要去公寓了
No! no, and don't bother showing up at the flat either,
因为我已经搬走了
Cause I've moved.
搬走了?  搬到哪去了?
Moved? where?
这无关紧要
It doesn't matter.
听着  Desmond  我要挂电话了
Look, Desmond, I'm going to go.
求你  不要再打来了
Please, just don't call me again.
别这样  听着  Penny  Penny  我...
No, no. no, listen. Penny, Penny, I ne--Penny, i
需要你
Need you.
你刚才...记起了什么吗  Desmond
Did you just... experience something, Desmond?
见鬼  Frank  你不能到这儿来
What the hell, Frank? you're not supposed to be down here,
-更不能和他一起来这  -抱歉  医生
And definitely not with him. sorry, doc,
但是我刚接了Faraday从岛上打来的电话
But I got Faraday calling from the island.
-他想和这个苏格兰人谈谈  -不行
He needs to talk to the scottish guy. no,
Faraday不会和我的病人谈的  快出去
Faraday's not talking to my patient. now get out of here.
但是他不是你的病人  快给Desmond电话
But he's not your patient. give Desmond the phone. hey!
快点把电话给他!
Give him the phone now!
喂?
Hello?
是Desmond吗  Desmond  我是Daniel Faraday
Desmond? Desmond, my name is Daniel Faraday.
昨天飞机起飞前我们见过
We met yesterday before you took off,
但是我想你不记得我了
But I'm guessing you don't remember that.
-对吗  -起飞?  什么
Am I right? took off? what?
Desmond  我们长话短说
Desmond, we don't have long to talk,
我要你告诉我你以为是哪一年
So I need you to tell me what year you think it is.
什么意思  什么我认为哪一年  是1996年
What do you mean, what year do I think--it's 1996.
很好  Desmond
All right, desmond.
Desmond  你得告诉我  你在哪
Desmond, look, you--you gotta tell me. where are you?
我在  我在一个什么医务室
I-i'm in-- I'm in some kind of sick bay.
不是  不是现在  Desmond
No, no, no. not right now, desmond.
你自己以为你在哪  是1996年你在哪
Where are you supposed to be? where are you in 1996?
我在军营  是一个苏格兰皇室军团
I-i'm at camp millar. it's, uh, royal scots regiment.
就在格拉斯哥北部  Dan  你想...
It's, uh, just north of glasgow. dan, you might wanna--
对  对  不  我想想  我想想
Y-yeah, yeah. no. no, I'm thinking. I'm thinking.
Desmond  听着
Desmond, listen,
如果再次发生  Desmond  我要你坐上火车
When it happens again, Desmond, I need you to get on a train.
坐火车去牛津
Get on a train and go to oxford.
去牛津大学
Oxford university.
女王学院的物理系  好吗
Queen's college physics department, all right?
什么  为什么
W-what? why?
因为我要你去找我
Because I need you to find me.
在哪里  在哪里
Where is it? where is it?
什么  我的日记  我的日记
What? my journal, my journal.
我要我的日记  或者我不相信他
I need my journal, or I won't believe him.
-为什么他以为他在1996年 -我不知道
Why does he think he's in 1996? I don't know. I don't know.
不可预知  是随机的原因
It's unpredictable. it's a random effect.
有时这种现象只会持续几个小时
Sometimes the displacement's only a couple of hours.
有时是几年
Sometimes it's years.
等等 等等  这以前发生过吗
Wait, wait, this has happened before?
电话给我  谢谢
The phone now, please. thank you.
-Desmond  还在吗  -医生  里面发生什么事了
Desmond, are you still there? doc? hey, doc, are you okay in there?
-快说!  我坚持不了多久  -是的  我在
Talk to him. I can't hold them for long. um, yes. yes, I'm here.
好  Desmond  听着  当你在女王学院找到我
Okay, Desmond, listen, when you find me at queen's college,
我要你告诉我把设备设置到2.342
I need you to tell me to set the device to 2.342.
-什么  -知道了吗  是2.342
What? all right, you got it? 2.342.
振荡必须设置为11赫兹
And it must be oscillating at 11 hertz.
知道了吗  Desmond
You got it, Desmond?
是2.342  振荡设为11...
2.342, oscillating at 11...
记住...记住是2.342和11赫兹  好吗
Just--just remember that-- 2.342 at 11 hertz, all right?
还有一件事  Desmond
And one more thing, Desmond.
如果数字还不能说服我的话
If the numbers don't convince me,
我要你告诉我你知道埃勒维兹
I need you to tell me that you know about Eloise.
嘿  放松点  放松点
Hey, hey, hey! easy, easy.
把电话给我
Get off the phone.
告诉我你记住了是埃勒维兹
Tell me that you know about Elo--
...不仅仅是原创的思想
...not a single piece of original thinking...
原创的概念是...
The concept of "original"--
就是派生的反义词
The opposite of derivative.
我是来给你留下印象的  Hollister先生
I am the one for you to impress, Mr. Hollister,
-我没印象  -那就再去试试
And I'm not impressed. so go. go try again.
抱歉  请问你是Daniel Faraday吗
Um, sorry, are--are you Daniel Faraday?
你是?
You are?
抱歉  我是  我是Desmond Hume
Uh, I'm sorry. I'm--i'm Desmond Hume, and, uh,
别人给我讲在这能找到你
I was told I could find you here.
我想我...
And I think I've...
我刚到过未来
I've just been to the future.
-未来?  -是的
The future? yes.
我在那和你说话
Uh, i-i spoke to you there.
你告诉我到这  牛津
You, uh, you told me to come here to--to oxford
你说  你可以帮我
You--you said you'd help me.
为什么我在未来不帮助你呢
Why didn't I just help you there in the future?
为什么我要把你送上时间旅行
Why would I put you through the headache of time traveling?
你知道我的意思吗
You--you know what I mean?
就感觉有点多此一举
It just seems a little... unnecessary?
你以为我那些受尊敬的同僚们
And don't you think my esteemed colleagues
会因为一点点的相信
Could've come up with something
而来找我吗
Just a little more believable, huh?
又是什么恶作剧?  时间上自相矛盾  毫无创见
What kind of a prank is that? time paradox--so uninspired.
把你的设备...设置到2.342
Set your device to, um... 2.342
然后确定振荡在11赫兹
And--and make sure it oscillates at 11.
好吧  你...
Okay, now--now you...
你告诉我是谁告诉你那些数字的
You're gonna tell me who told you those numbers.
是你
You did.
不可能  这完全是荒谬可笑的
No, this is... this is ridiculous.
我知道埃勒维兹
I know about Eloise.
这些到底是什么
What--what is all this?
这就是我做令牛津不舒服的事情的地方
This is where I do the things oxford frowns upon.
好  那么未来的我
All right, this... this future version of me,
提到了我们这次会面  对吗?  一定提到过
Uh, he--he referenced this meeting, right? obviously.
所以我一定会记得你来过这里  是吧
So--so I would remember you coming to oxford, right?
我会记得这件事情  在此时此刻
I would remember this, here, right now.
实际上你不记得
Actually, um, no.
-不记得了?  -也许你就是忘了
No? maybe you just forgot.
说的对  这怎么可能发生过?
Yeah, right. how would that happen?
那么你现在要改变未来?
So this--this is changing the future?
你不可能改变未来
You can't change the future.
-那是干嘛的?  -防辐射
What's that for? radiation.
-我也要穿吗?  -你不需要
Do I get one? you don't need one.
穿它是为了防护过量辐射  我每天要做20次
For prolonged exposure. i-i do this 20 times a day.
你不用戴什么保护头吗
So what do you put on your head?
是的
Yeah.
这个
This...
它是Eloise
This is Eloise.
你这是在做什么
What does this do?
这  如果你给我的数字是正确的
This... if the numbers you gave me are correct,
这将使Eloise
What this will do...
摆脱连续时空的限制
Is unstick Eloise in time,
就像你一样
Just like you.
发生了什么
What happened?
等等 别说话  她还没醒过来
Wait, shh, shh. she's not back yet.
好的  就看马上会有什么结果
Okay, here goes... everything.
动起来  动起来
Come on, come on. come on.
对了
That's it.
对了  这就对了
That's it. that's it.
好  好
Yes, yes.
成功了!
It worked!
-这太不可思议了  -抱歉  等一下
Th-this is incredible. I'm sorry.
一只老鼠能跑出你这破迷宫有什么稀奇?
How is a rat running through a bloody maze so incredible?
不可思议的是
What is incredible
我今天早上刚做的这个迷宫
Is I just finished the maze this morning,
我原打算到从现在开始的一小时后
And I'm not gonna teach her how to run it
才教她怎么跑过这个迷宫
Until an hour from now.
这么说你刚才把它送到了未来
S-so--so you--you sent her to the future.
不  只是她的意识  思想
No, no, no, her consciousness, her mind.
这对我有什么帮助
So-- so how does that help me?
你?  帮助你?
You? help you?
我不明白  是我应该帮助你吗?
I don't understand. am I supposed to help you?
-难道我不是把你送回这里来帮助我吗  -我不知道你为什么让我来这
Didn't I send you back here to help me? I don't know why you sent me here.
我所知道的只有
All I know about you is you--
你最后困在了一个可怕的岛上
You end up on some bloody island.
什么岛?  为什么我会在一个岛上
What island? w-why would I go to an i--
Desmond  把电话给我
Desmond, give me the phone.
都怎么了  大家冷静一点!
Hey, come on! everybody relax!
听着  Daniel要给那个人打电话
Listen, look, Daniel wanted to talk to the guy,
-我们就把电话给他了  就是这样  -你让Faraday和他说话了?
So we brought him the phone, that's all. you let Faraday talk to him?
-他说他能帮上忙  -Faraday连自己都帮不了!
He said he could help. faraday can't even help himself!
出去  船长要跟你谈话
Outside now. the captain wants to talk to you.
-我也要跟你们船长谈一谈  -我一定会告诉他的
And I want to talk to your captain. I'll be sure to let him know.
还有  你们老老实实坐着
In the meantime, have a seat.
-去哪  那个岛?  -他说能帮得上忙
Back where? the island? he said he could help.
-他说他会告诉我需要去做什么  -Desmond  Desmond
He said he--he'd tell me what I needed to do. Desmond, Desmond,
你能给我解释一下
Can you please explain to me--
Desmond?
你叫Desmond?
You're Desmond?
我认识你吗
Do I know you?
我是George Minkowski
I'm George Minkowski.
我是信号联络负责人
I'm the communications officer.
在他们把我绑在这之前
Before they strapped me down here,
我在信号室负责调度这艘船
All the calls to and from this boat came through me
所有的电信联络
In the radio room.
我经常
And every so often,
能看到信号灯在我的控制台上闪烁
I'd get this flashing light on my console--
有一个电话打进来
An incoming call.
我们被严令不许接听那个电话
We were under strict orders never to answer it.
那么你说的和我有什么关系
So? what's that got to do with me?
是你女朋友打来的
Those calls came from your girlfriend.
Penelope Widmore
Penelope widmore.
发生了什么事
What happened?
你醒了
Oh, uh, you're back.
你刚刚昏迷了大约有75分钟
And... you were out almost 75 minutes.
是的
Oh, yeah. yeah, yeah. you just... whew.
你刚说话的时候突然就摊在了地上
You went catatonic right in the middle of a sentence.
我只好把你扶到椅子上
I had to carry you to the chair.
-我想你刚才又回到了未来  -是吧
So I take it you were-- you were in the future again? aye.
-多长时间  -我不知道  五分钟?
For how long? I don't know. five minutes?
为什么这种情况总在发生
Why does this keep happening?
我猜想你的请况
Uh, in your case,
应该症状呈指数级加重
I'm guessing the progression is exponential.
每一次你的意识穿梭时空
Each time your consciousness jumps,
都会变得更难以回到初始状态
It gets harder and harder to jump back.
如果我是你的话  过马路一定小心翼翼
I would be careful crossing the street if I were you.
她怎么了  死了
What happened to her? she died.
-我知道她死了  怎么死的?  -也许是脑动脉瘤  我还不确定
Yeah, I can see that. how? brain aneurysm, probably. I don't know.
我待会给她验尸
I'm going to do an autopsy later.
我也会死吗
Is that gonna happen to me?
不同的个体受到的影响应该会有区别  但是
The effects seem to vary from case to case, but, uh...
快告诉我!
Answer me!
如果这种状况持续下去  我会不会死掉
If this keeps happening, am I gonna die?
我想
I think...
Eloise是脑梗阻
Eloise's brain short-circuited.
在现在和未来之间的频繁穿梭
The jumps between the present and the future--
她最终不能分辨出现在和未来
She eventually--she couldn't tell which was which.
-她没有能支撑自己穿梭时空的东西  -什么是anchor
She had no anchor. wh-what do you mean, "anchor"?
可以将两个时点联系起来的东西
Something familiar in both times.
所有这些  看到了吗  它们都是变量
All this--see this? this is all variables.
随机的  混乱的
It's random. it's chaotic.
所有的方程都需要稳定性  一些已知量
Every equation needs stability, something known.
就是常量
It's called a constant.
Desmond  你没有常量
Desmond, you have no constant.
当你穿梭到了未来  你对熟悉所有的事物都不熟悉
When you go to the future, nothing there is familiar.
如果你想阻止它再次发生
So if you want to stop this,
就要在未来找一样你珍视的事物
Y--then you need to find something there,
它一直深藏在你的内心深处
Something that you really, really care about...
同时存在于现在这个时点
That also exists back here...
1996年
In 1996.
这个常量
This constant...
它可以是一个人吗
Can it be a person?
对  可以
Yeah, maybe.
但你一定要和这个人取得联系
But you have to make some kind of contact.
你刚才不是说你在一艘
Didn't you say you were
不知道在什么方位的船上吗
Off on a boat in the middle of nowhere?
你在给谁打电话
Uh... who are you calling?
我在给我珍惜的常量
I'm calling my bloody constant.
你所拨打的号码
The number you have dialed
无法接通
Has been disconnected.
你还好吗
You okay?
你看上去老了不少  是吧
You look a lot older now, huh?
欢迎回来  Desmond
Welcome back, Desmond.
-我要给Penny打电话  -给你女朋友打电话可不是当务之急
I need to call Penny. calling your girlfriend is not our priority.
听着兄弟  我不大认识你  但
Listen, brother, I don't know you, but--
你貌似认识我
But you seem to know me,
如果我和你是朋友
So--so if you and me are friends,
那么我需要你的帮助  我现在就要给Penny打电话
Then I need your help. I need to call Penny now.
小伙子们  你们可根本没弄清楚情况
Whoa! you boys are gettin' way ahead of yourselves.
两天前  有个人毁掉了所有的设备
Two days ago, someone sabotaged all the equipment.
我们与陆地失去了所有的联系
We lost all communication with the mainland.
我当时有可能修好它  但后来
I probably could've fixed it, but then...
我成了疯子
Then I went nuts.
信号室在哪儿
Where's the radio room?
在上面一层  我带你们去  快点
It's one deck up. I'll take you there. come on.
我们怎么才能离开这儿
And how do we get out of here?
门开了
Through the door.
貌似你俩在这船上还有朋友
Looks like you guys have a-a friend on this boat.
现在没人
It's clear.
"the black rock"从朴次茅斯港出发的
"the black rock" set sail
英国船  1845年3月22日
From portsmouth, english, march 22, 1845,
前往暹罗(泰国旧称)进行交易
On a trading mission to the kingdom of siam
不幸在海中走失
When she was tragically lost at sea.
这次旅行留下来的唯一见证物
The only known artifact of this journey
就是船上第一大副的日记
Is the journal of the ship's first mate,
它是七年后在马达加斯加岛的
Which was discovered among the artifacts of pirates
海盗船的遗物中被发现
On the sainte marie, Madagascar, seven years later.
日记的内容从来没有被公开过
The contents of this journal have never been made public,
或者被出售人家族以外的其他人所知晓
Nor are known to anyone outside the family of the seller,
Tovard Hanso
Tovard Hanso.
我们以15万英镑起拍这件
We open the bidding on lot 2-3-4-2
编号2-3-4-2的拍品
At 150,000 pounds.
这位先生  出价15万
150,000, sir.
16万?  有人出16万吗?
160,000? do I hear 160,000?
16万  17万
160,000, sir. 170,000, sir.
有人致电出价18万
180,000 on the phone.
20万
200,000 pounds.
22万镑
220,000 pounds.
24万
240,000.
26万
260,000 pounds, sir.
28万
280,000.
有人致电出价30万  32万
On the phone, I have 300,000-- 320,000.
34万镑
340,000 pounds.
36万  38万  38万英镑...
360,000. 380,000. 380,000 pounds...
-拍卖是要提前预约的  先生  -有人出价40万镑吗?
This auction's by appointment only, sir. do I hear 400,000 pounds?
哥们  是这样子的  我只是想
Yeah, listen, pal, I just need to speak
-和那位先生说句话  -不好意思  先生
To the gentleman over there just for a moment, okay? I'm sorry, sir.
成交...  38万镑售予755号买主  谢谢
Sold... for 380,000 pounds to bidder 7-5-5. thank you.
只要一点时间  好吗?  听着...
Just for a minute, all right? look--
Widmore. Desmond先生?
Mr. widmore. desmond?
-能和你说句话吗  先生?  -对不起  Widmore先生  他...
Can I have a word, sir? I'm sorry, mr. widmore. he--
-哦  没事...  -这是Charles Dickens死时的财产
No, no, it's fine. ...possession of charles dickens when he died.
-跟我来  -我们开始竞拍此件物品...
Walk with me. we open the bidding on this lot...
说吧  想说什么
Your word. let's have it.
我要和Penny联系
I need to get in touch with penny.
我不知道如何联系她
I don't know how to reach her,
她的号码已经无效了
And her number's been disconnected.
曾经有段时间  如果你向她求婚的话
There was a time when if you'd have asked her to marry you,
我确信她一定会答应的
I'm certain she would've said yes.
但幸运的是...
Fortunately...
你的怯懦赢得了上风
Your cowardice won out instead.
我将此视为你又改变主意了
I take it you've had second thoughts.
你希望她能再给你一次机会
And you'd like her to give you another chance.
为什么你这么恨我?
Why do you hate me so much?
恨你的不是我
It's not me who hates you.
这是她的地址
Here's her address.
让她自己告诉你吧
I'll let her tell you herself.
Desmond
Desmond.
我知道  越来越难了
I know. it's getting harder.
而且这种情况开始更快出现了
It starts happening faster, too.
来吧  行动吧
Come on. let's move.
喂  这怎么会发生在你身上的?
Hey, how did this happen to you?
我们在此下锚  等待命令
We were anchored here, waiting for our orders,
闷得要命
Bored out of our minds.
Brandon和我  他是其中一名船员
Me and brandon-- he's one of the crew members--
我们...我们驾着交通船
We--we took out the ship's tender.
我们就是想看看这个岛
We just wanted to see the island.
但是Brandon开始发疯
But brandon started acting crazy,
所以我们只能回返
So we had to turn around.
他在哪里?  运尸袋里
Where is he? in a body bag.
那里
There.
谁干的?
Who did this?
这可问住我了
You got me.
但当船长发现的时候  我感觉很抱歉...
But when the captain finds out, I feel sor--
你打完电话后  最好有人能告诉我
After your call, someone has to tell me
到底是怎么回事
Precisely what is going on.
兄弟  你能修好吗?
Can you fix it, brother?
需要一点时间
I need a minute.
你有号码?
Do you have the number to make the call?
George?
醒醒  兄弟  醒醒  你得醒过来
Wake up, brother. wake up. you've gotta come back.
-你得醒过来  -Desmond  你知道号码吗?
You've gotta come back. desmond, do you know the number?
-不记得  -你最好能记住它
No. well, you'd better remember it.
现在是2004年
It's 2004.
我都没意识到快到圣诞节了  过了这么...
I didn't realize it was almost christmas. it's been...
Desmond
Desmond.
不
No! uhh!
我不能...
I can't...
回...
Get...
来了
Back.
他怎么了?
What happened to him?
同样要发生在我身上的事情
The same thing that's gonna happen to me.
你怎么来了?
What are you doing here?
我必须来...我是说  我尽力联系你
I had to--i mean, I tried to call you,
-但是打电话联系不上你  -是  因为我搬家了
But you--you disconnected your phone. yeah, because I moved.
听着  我不知道你是否意识到
Look, I don't know if you're getting the signals, desmond,
但是我想和你完全断绝关系
But I'm trying to make a clean break from you,
-所以  如果你不介意  我要...  -等等  等等  Pen
So if you don't mind, I'm gonna-- wait, wait, wait, wait. pen,
请等一下
Please wait.
我只是...我只是需要你的新号码  好吗?
I just--i just need to get your new phone number, okay?
因为我...我犯了一个大错
Because i-i made a huge mistake.
我...我本不应和你分手  而且...  而且...
I-i should never have broken up with you, and--and--and... ugh.
我知道...我现在知道了  对不起  不要  请不要
I know--i know that now, and--and I'm sorry and-- oh, don't. just don't--
我知道  我也知道...
I understand, and--and i-i know
可是已经太晚了  难以挽回
It's--it's too late to change things,
但是我得告诉你
But I need to tell you something,
而且...而且我需要你听我说
And--and I need you to listen to me, and...
听着  我...我知道那会听起来很荒谬  但是...
Look, i-i know it's gonna sound ridiculous, but...
求你了  Pen
Please, pen.
请你听我说
I need you to listen to me.
说吧  说完就走
Just say what you need to say and then go.
我知道这不可理解
I know this doesn't make any sense,
因为我都不相信
Because it doesn't make any sense to me,
但是8年之后  我...
But eight years from now, i...
我需要给你打电话
I-i need to call you,
但是如果没有你的号码  就打不成电话
And I can't call you if I don't have your number.
什么?
What?
听着  Penny  只用...只用告诉我你的号码
Look, penny, just-- just give me your number.
我...我知道  我知道我把事情都搞砸了
I-i know-- I know I've ruined things.
我知道你认为我们之间已经完了  但其实不是的
I know you think things are over between us, but they're not.
如果你对我们之间尚有一点信心  就请...
If there's any part of you that still believes in us, just...
就告诉我号码吧
Just give me your number.
我怎么知道你会不会今晚或明天打给我...
And what's to say you wouldn't call me tonight or tomorrow--
我不会
I won't call...
在8年之内打电话给你
For eight years.
2004年12月24号
December the 24th, 2004.
圣诞夜
Christmas eve.
我保证
I promise.
求你了  Pen
Please, pen.
如果我给你号码  你会走吗?
If I give you the number, will you leave?
7946-0893
7946-0893.
7946-0893. 7946...
够了  你不准备写下来吗
All that, and you're not gonna write it down?
没什么用  你一定要一直用这个号码
It wouldn't do any good. you have to keep that number.
-在8年内你不要换号码  -出去  出去
You can't change your number for eight years. just get out. get out!
请记住...请记住  2004年12月24日
Just--just remember, december the 24th, 2004.
听着  Pen  如果...如果你还在意我
Look, pen, if--if you still care about me,
你一定要回答  我没疯  Penny
You have to answer. I'm not crazy, penny!
你要相信我的话  你要...你要
You have to believe me! you have--you have to
信任我
Trust me.
我的确信任你  但你还是必须记住那个号码
I do trust you, but you still have to remember that number.
7946-0893
7946-0893.
7946-0893  这是在伦敦的电话号码
7946-0893. it's a london number.
时机正好
Excellent timing.
话筒好了
The patch is done,
但是不知道电池能撑多久
But I don't know how long the battery will last.
我希望她在
I hope she's there.
我也希望
I hope so, too.
你好?
Hello?
Penny?
Desmond?!
Penny  你接电话了
Penny. penny, you answered.
你接电话拉  Penny
You answered, penny.
Des  你在哪里?
Des, where are you?
我在...
I'm...
我在...我在一个船上  嗯...
I'm... I'm--i'm on a boat. um...
我一直在一个岛上  Pen
I've--i've been on an island, pen.
天啊  Penny  真的是你吗?
My god, penny, is that really you?
是啊
Yeah!
是  是我
Yes, it's me!
你相信我的话了
You believed me.
你依旧很在意我
You still care about me. des...
在过去的3年里  我一直在找你
I've been looking for you for the past three years.
我知道那个岛
I know about the island.
我研究过...
I've been research--
当我和你的朋友Charlie说的时候...
And then when I spoke to your friend charlie...
那时我才知道你还活着
That's when I knew you were still alive.
那时我才知道我没发疯
That's when I knew I wasn't crazy.
Des  你还在听吗?
Des, are you still there?
是!  我还在  你能听到我说话?
Yes! yes, I'm here! I'm still here. can you hear me? yeah, yeah,
效果好点了
That's better.
我爱你  Penny
I love you, penny.
我一直都爱着你
I've always loved you.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
我不知道我身处何方  但是...
I don't know where I am, but...
我会找到你的...  我保证...
I'll find you, des... I promise...
无论如何...我会回到你身边
No matter what... I'll come back to you.
我不会放弃的  我保证
I won't give up. I promise.
我保证  我爱你  我爱你
I promise. I love you. I love you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
电池没电了  那是我们仅有的电池
The power source went dead. that's all we have.
谢谢你  Sayid
Thank you, sayid.
已经足够了
It was enough.
你还好吧?
Are you all right now?
非常好
I'm perfect.